{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I drink tea",
      "answer": "ich trinke tee"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: You play cricket",
      "answer": "du spielst cricket"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: He cooks Pasta",
      "answer": "er kocht pasta"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We learn",
      "answer": "wir lernen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: They sing",
      "answer": "sie singen"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Ich ______ Brot. ",
      "answer": "esse"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Du ______ Fu√üball. ",
      "answer": "spielst"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Er ______ Pasta. ",
      "answer": "kocht"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Wir ______ Deutsch.",
      "answer": "lernen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: Sie ______ ein Lied. (Lied = song)",
      "answer": "singen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I sing Macarena",
      "answer": "ich singe macarena"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: He plays cricket",
      "answer": "er spielt cricket "
    }
  ]
}
